Chester's Mill is a place
like any other.
At least, it used to be...
until we were cut off
from the rest of the world
by a mysterious dome.
Invisible, indestructible,
and completely inescapable.
We're trapped.
We don't know
where it came from
or why it's here,
but now that we're all trapped
under the dome together,
none of our secrets are safe.
Who the hell are you?
Barbie. People
just call me Barbie.
It's a nickname.
My husband isn't here,
but he'll turn up, you'll see.
What do we do when the people
start asking about the propane?
That's your business.
Duke, is it your pacemaker?
Stop!
No one can hear us
all the way down here.
Let me out of here!
Junior.
Dad.
You can stay with me.
Come on, I'll give you the nickel tour.
Where is it?
I don't have it!
Yeah? My boss is not
gonna like that.
You got one day.
You hear me?
Listen, all you've
got to do is pay up.
You might want to think
about it, all right?
I mean, you don't want
to do anything stupid.
Yeah?
You all right?
Yep. Fine.
You were, uh,
talking in your sleep.
Yelling, actually.
Is that thing still out there?
Yeah, looks like it.
The Hazmat suits haven't left.
Julia...
thanks again
for letting me crash here.
With my husband missing,
and everything
that happened today...
it was nice to have the company.
I'll see you in the morning.
Great.
Did you lose something?
Yeah. You didn't
happen to see
a pair of dog tags
around anywhere, did you?
No.
But I'll keep an eye out.
Night.
Linda! Linda!
What the hell happened?
Who shot Duke?
No one shot Duke, Paul.
Calm down.
He just got close
to this thing,
and his pacemaker exploded.
Ah!
Holy...
If this thing
blows up mechanical things,
then why didn't
Freddy's watch explode?
It's a wind-up.
It must only affect things
with batteries.
Either way,
just check the roadblocks
and make sure nobody gets
near this thing.
Well, who's in charge now?
You're a cop. Do your job.
What about me?
We need to take care of Duke.
Joe, wait up!
I'm fine.
No, you're not.
An hour ago,
you were having a seizure,
flopping around
like a fish on a hook.
Did I say anything?
Yeah, something about... stars.
Pink stars.
Anything you want to tell me?
No.
Hey!
Any luck, you guys?
No, not yet!
This thing goes down far.
Oh, my God, you know
what all this means?
We're so not having
that trig test tomorrow.
Trig.
That's a great idea.
It is?
I can totally map this thing,
see if there's any holes.
I'm coming with you.
Dude, you don't have to.
Buddy, Lewis had Clark,
you got me, all right?
Come on.
Say...
did you hear anything more
about the military
- on that contraption of yours?
- Nope.
I lost the signal,
but I'm trying to get it back.
It's not as easy as cuing up
the next Van Halen track.
Now, why is it that engineers
always act superior to DJs?
Because we're smarter, Phil.
Negative, sir,
fire is ineffective
against the surface.
But we can confirm
there is no radioactivity
emanating from the dome.
They did it again.
Second time in 24 hours
they called it a dome.
Yeah, I heard him.
No, I don't think you did,
because you'd be
freaking out, too.
We're under a dome, Dodee.
Now, this is not just
some invisible wall
where a chopper can drop
in and rescue us, man.
We gotta tell people.
And we will.
It's just right now
we only know enough
to scare the crap out of them.
To be continued.
♪ Up to second gear,
then come back down ♪
♪ Daddy call his boss...
Faithful insomniacs,
Phil Bushey here.
It's been a long night.
And if you're listening to me,
it's because
you've got no choice.
You see, this barrier thing
is blocking
all of the cell phones,
TV, Internet...
everything in our humble burg
of Chester's Mill.
Now, theories about
what's causing this
range from the North Koreans
to a breach
in the space-time continuum...
Well, sorry I didn't
get to you sooner, Rose.
Had to make sure the clinic
and the nursing home
were taken care of.
Are you kidding me?
If you're not careful,
people are gonna start
calling you Santa Claus.
Oh, God bless you, Jim Rennie.
How much do I owe you?
Ho, ho, ho.
Oh, my God.
The lights are back.
Did that invisible wall
come down?
Well, I'm afraid not.
But, uh, we've got gennies
up and running,
so we have some power,
at least get back to
some sense of normal.
I don't believe we've met.
Councilman Jim
Rennie, this is Carolyn
and, uh, her partner Alice.
They're staying
in my spare room upstairs.
They're in from L.A.
We got trapped driving
through your little town.
We were taking our daughter Norrie to...
To camp.
But we have to get out of here.
Our daughter is sick.
She had a seizure.
Does your girl have epilepsy?
No. It can happen to anyone.
Caffeine,
sleep deprivation.
I've seen it in my patients.
She's a psychiatrist.
Well, I'm sorry you ladies
aren't discovering
Chester's Mill
under better circumstances,
but trust me,
if you're gonna be
stuck somewhere,
this is the place to be.
I've lived here my entire life,
and, uh...
...no place
I'd rather call home.
Jim.
I need you to come with me.
Duke's dead.
Look at me, damn it!
Anyone?
I wouldn't even bother.
I mean, you could strip naked
in front of these guys,
they're still not
gonna pay attention.
I tried that an hour ago.
They didn't even blink.
Oh.
I looked around, by the way,
but no sign of your dog tags.
Oh, yeah, no worries.
You know what?
I probably just left
them in my car.
So what makes you think
these guys are under orders
not to talk to us?
Because they're
not talking to us.
Maybe they did this, you know.
Maybe they're responsible.
And why would they do that?
I don't know.
Could be, uh, an experiment.
Some sort of portable
detention camp.
Maybe we're being used
as guinea pigs.
Whatever it is,
these guys are the reason
my husband is trapped
out there!
ere you heading?
The radio station.
They might not
be talking to us,
but they are talking
to somebody.
I told you, you're safe with me.
Mr. Rennie!
Help! Help!
Angie...
my dad's not home.
Mr. Rennie!
My dad's not home!
Let go of me!
Let go!
No... no!
No!
No! No!
Ah! N...
Get... off.
Get...
What the hell do you want from me?
Look, I just want you
to go back to being
the Angie I knew
before yesterday.
We were doing great,
and then this thing
comes down and you...
you tell me to take a hike.
I think it scrambled your brain.
One of us has a scrambled brain,
all right.
You can't see it, but I can.
You're sick, Angie.
But I'm gonna make you better.
If I'm so sick,
then why don't you take me
to the hospital?
If you care about me so much?
Because he might
still be there.
Who might still be here?
The guy I saw you with.
What guy?
Yesterday?
Outside the hospital?
Barbie?
The guy who came in
with Mrs. Shumway?
I don't even know him.
Don't play dumb with me, Ange,
I can see right through you.
All he did was
give me a cigarette.
Uh-huh.
What did I ever do to you?!
You loved me.
No.
Junior...
I never...
Yes, Angie, you did.
And when this thing comes down,
you're gonna love me again.
I will never love you!
You were right.
That guy...
at the hospital,
we didn't just share
a cigarette.
He screwed my brains out,
and I loved it.
I loved it more
than I ever did with you.
You'll never be the man
that he is.
Junior!
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Holy hell.
He was a good man.
I loved him.
He was like a father to me.
He was a good friend.
You know, just before he died,
he tried to tell me something.
Tried telling you what?
He said there were things
that I didn't know
about Chester's Mill.
Things that he needed
to protect me from.
What did that mean?
I wish I could tell you.
What am I gonna do
with another body?
The cemetery is
outside the barrier,
and my freezer's full.
Show some respect.
This isn't just another body.
This is Duke Perkins.
What's that?
Turn up your hearing aid,
Lester.
I said this is Duke Perkins.
Oh, no.
Oh, good Lord. He's Duke Perkins.
Deputy Esquivel,
I'm so sorry for your loss.
Thank you, Reverend Coggins.
I should get back out there.
Well, you're right, Linda.
Go out there and do your job.
I'll make sure Duke here
gets taken care of.
You're using our stuff.
You're high as a kite.
So what? It's Judgment Day, Jim.
I might as well be feeling
the Rapture.
The only reason we got into this
was to try to save
Chester's Mill.
No.
That's the reason Duke went
along with it.
You and I,
we had other priorities.
All right?
I mean...
I mean, at least now,
we don't have to worry
about him talking.
Real man of God there, Rev.
Come on, let's go.
What? Where are we going?
Clean up our mess.
Dude, found a way out.
Check it.
You're such an idiot.
It's Joe, right?
Yeah, McAlister.
Dude, this is the
guy who saved my ass
when that plane went down.
He totally said
it was raining arms and legs.
Yeah, you could say that.
What are you up to?
So far, I marked these points,
and by measuring the distance
between them,
I was able to come up
with the Y coordinate,
and then by multiplying it
by its K integer...
He connected the dots.
It's totally gonna be circle.
So far, it looks like
it's about ten miles across.
It covers the entire Mill,
including some
of Lake Eastpointe.
And you did this?
Yeah, but we're being
really careful.
Keep it up.
Where'd that guy come from?
Definitely not from around here.
How do you know?
'Cause he's cool.
Come on, Dodee,
you just had him.
Patience, Philip.
Did you get something?
Shh.
Air traffic has been
rerouted around Chester's Mill
until further notice.
Continue to monitor
the airspace.
What the hell is that?
Jim.
What are you doing?
I was, um,
looking for that.
It's Duke's will.
Go ahead, read it.
He, uh,
left me his house.
Everything.
Of course he did.
He treated you like the daughter
he never had.
Now what do we do?
It was a close call.
No thanks to you.
What was I supposed to do,
phone you?
So what'd you find out?
Nothing to do with propane.
Duke must have kept the records
at his house.
Yeah, but it's not
his house anymore.
He left it to the girl.
So you better get over there
before she does.
Me?
What are you gonna do?
My job, Lester.
Now get out.
I'm the only councilman
left in Chester's Mill.
I got a town to take care of.
You made this?
Yeah, I'm only
three credits short
of my master's degree
in electrical engineering.
Wow. How does it work?
Well, this is a harmonic
microwave frequency converter.
It turns low frequency waves
into high frequency waves
so that we can hear them.
Maybe you should just
let me hear it?
Okay.
Um, sometimes it's
hard to pick up.
Further tests reveal
dome appears to be impervious
to high energy lasers
and all class-A
corrosive chemicals.
We're under a dome.
Yeah, that's what
they keep calling it.
Why haven't you told anybody?
We're not a news station.
Hey, Phil?
And that was some
face-melting rock and roll
brought to you by...
I'm going on.
I tried to stop her.
I'm sorry, what are you doing?
I'm going on the air.
No, you can't.
This is Julia Shumway
from the weekly Independent.
I have some news for all of us
stuck here inside
Chester's Mill.
I have just learned
that the barrier
around Chester's Mill
is being called a dome.
This information appears
to be coming
from military sources
positioned just
outside Chester's Mill,
just outside the dome.
We will keep updating you
as information comes in.
So stay tuned to...
WYBS.
Your only source of news
from under the dome.
What does that mean?
I have no idea.
I do, Mom.
It means we're all gonna die
in here.
This dome
thing, how big is it?
No idea.
We're under a dome?
Are we gonna run
out of air?
Until I find out
where Julia got
this information,
I think it's best
that we just all stay calm.
What if it collapses on us?
Great, now the sky is falling.
If we keep our heads
and we stick together,
we'll get through this.
Hey, "We'll get through this"?
Huh? You don't know what
this dome thing might do.
You're right, but the last
thing we need right now
is for people to panic.
That thing took Duke.
Who's next?
Pull yourself together
and get out on patrol.
People are scared, and
when people are scared,
they start acting stupid.
Yeah, you'd have to be stupid
not to be scared.
You know,
I just hope someone tries
to blow this damn thing up.
Do you think
he's gonna be okay?
He's got to be.
We're gonna need
every man we got.
Think we'll ever see him again?
Who, Rusty?
Come on, Linda.
My brother's not gonna let
some magic bubble thing
keep him from seeing you again.
Yeah, that is Rusty.
Hey, you know what?
I probably shouldn't be
telling you this,
but he's taking you to Hawaii
for your honeymoon.
That dog told me that I had
to settle for Niagara Falls.
Reverend.
Hey.
How you holding up?
We got our hands full,
but I think we'll make it.
Yeah, you're in my prayers.
Julia Shumway,
back with an update.
Additional reports suggest
that the dome
is not radioactive,
but residents are advised
to continue to keep
a safe distance.
And now, something
to take our minds
off all this trouble.
What?
Hey!
Hey! Hey, stop! Stop!
What the hell are you doing?
I'm digging my way out.
No, you're not.
What the hell?
Any machine touches that dome,
you're fried.
Says who?
Duke.
His pacemaker blew right
out of his chest.
He's dead.
Duke's dead?
Who's in charge?
What if we're trapped
in here forever?
I'll never get to make out
with Mila Kunis.
I don't think this thing
is the only thing keeping
that from happening.
Just think about it.
We could have met every girl
we're ever gonna meet.
That is so depressing.
What the hell?
They're doing tests.
Must be checking to see
if water can come through.
Doesn't look good.
We're screwed.
Wait.
It's like a sieve.
What the hell's a sieve?
A strainer, douche.
Like-like for pasta?
So it does let water through?
Yeah, just a little.
Maybe we can get through.
Aren't we, like, 70% water?
Yeah, it's the other 30%
that's the problem, genius.
This and, uh, can you give
me a pack of filtered?
Actually, you know what?
Make it three.
Anything else?
No, that's it.
Thank you.
Didn't anyone ever tell you
smoking's bad for you?
Hey, no,
these-these aren't for me.
It's an investment.
We end up getting stuck
in here for a while,
you would be surprised
what people will swap
for these things.
So I'd probably hang onto
that candy bar if I were you.
What's wrong?
You had it working before.
It's not like punching in
the presets on your car radio.
This takes finesse.
Finesse, my ass.
She's just diddling.
Sometimes she gets lucky.
Further tests
reveal the dome appears
to be impervious
to high-energy laser.
How's that for lucky?
Shh.
This is Mobile Ground Unit 2.
After exhaustive testing we are
unable to determine the origin
or the composition of the dome.
Oh, my God,
the military doesn't know
what it is.
So?
So it means they didn't do it.
They're not responsible.
Who is?
Empty.
Come on. Come on.
Hey.
What have you got there?
Why are you following me?
So, this is where you did it.
I don't know what the hell
you're talking about.
This is where you screwed her.
I know all about you and Angie.
Who's Angie?
Don't act like you don't know.
Looks like she put up
a pretty good fight.
She belongs to me.
That's too bad for her.
She still belongs to me.
You just stay
the hell away from me.
Or what?
The next time,
I'm not gonna stop.
Ah!
Ah...
The Lord works
in mysterious ways.
Ah-ah! Ah!
Ah!
Help! No! Lord, help!
Aw, man.
His master must've been
right here.
Someone must've dragged
the rest of the body away.
Poor fella.
The dog's the poor fella?
I kind of feel sorrier
for the cut-in-half dude.
His name's Truman.
What're we gonna do with him?
We can't just leave him here.
Holy crap. Look.
A fire.
Let's go check it out.
Come on, Truman!
You almost killed us!
I got something for you.
Paul, what are you thinking?
This town is one click away from
total and complete lawlessss.
When the time comes, I'm ready,
and you should be, too.
We're on the same side here.
Yeah, for now.
Who the hell are you?!
Easy. That's the guy
that saved the McAlister kid
when the plane
crashed in the dome.
Linda, you there?
Get out here so I can
see you. Come here.
Go ahead, Jackie.
Sarah Martin just drove over.
She says there's a fire
at 223 Pretty Valley Road.
Oh, my God, that's Duke's house.
Get every warm body out there
to help.
You can kiss it good-bye--
the entire Chester's Mill's
fire department's out there
and we're in here.
Put that rifle down
and get your ass to Duke's.
You're not my boss.
Now.
You, warm body. Get in.
Any fire trucks still here?
Rusty and his buddies
took them all to Westlake
for that damn parade.
Clear the line
and get to Duke's.
Damn it, Coggins.
Where's the fire department?
Right over here! Come on!
Right now, they're coming.
Hey, stay back! Stay back!
Stay back!
Help! Help!
Somebody, somebody help me!
Get out of the way!
What are you doing here?
I heard it on the scanner.
What happened?
I have no idea.
I'm just glad Duke lived alone.
Come on. Everyone,
please stand back.
Come on.
Keep a safe distance.
We have to put this out.
How the hell are we gonna
do that?
You guys still got your
water pressure, right?
So, go and get as many
garden hoses as you can.
Go. Go-go-go-go-go-go.
Hey, guys, we need hoses.
Go. Go get water.
Whose got a hose?
Whose is that right there?
Grab your hose!
Excuse me.
Brian, your hose!
Backyard!
Barbie.
It hasn't rained in weeks.
We're inside a damn tinderbox.
If those flames spread
to any of these other houses,
it's gonna take
Chester's Mill and us with it.
Hey, everybody who does
not have a garden hose,
I want you to go get a bucket,
get a pot,
get-get a trash can, something.
Anything that can hold water.
Let's go.
Let's go, get buckets!
Help. Please help me!
Someone's inside.
Linda!
Somebody help me!
Help!
Anybody in here?!
Hello?!
Linda!
- You okay?
-  Yeah.
What the hell was Coggins
doing in Duke's house?
I don't know.
Where did Jim go?
- I don't know.
- Get out of here, guys.
There's a propane tank
next to the house.
Oh, my God, that's
a propane tank!
Let's go, let's go,
get out of here.
Come on, get him out.
Go, go!
The flames are too high.
The hoses aren't cutting it.
The fire is
spreading to the shrubs.
Get another hose over there.
There's not
enough water pressure.
Can you imagine our
neighbors back in Brentwood
helping out this way?
I don't even know
who our neighbors are.
We got to go faster.
Vic, you holding up all right?
Come on, guys, that's right.
Just like that. We got to get
more water on this thing,
all right? Come on.
Keep going.
Keep going, everyone.
We got to get more water.
Come on.
Faster, faster.
Keep at it, people.
The fire is spreading
to the fence.
The house will be next.
Deputy, give me a hand.
Over there, the
bottom of the fence.
Bottom of the fence.
Get more buckets!
Get some buckets in here.
The car's on fire.
Guys, back, everybody back.
This isn't gonna work.
It's like playing Whac-a-Mole.
As long as Duke's house
is burning,
the fire is just gonna
keep jumping.
Then it's over.
Or not. Hey, make some room!
Let's go!
Clear the street.
Get out of the street.
Let's go.
Hey, back up.
Everybody get back.
Let's go.
What the hell is Big Jim doing?
Is he insane?
He's gonna tear down
Duke's house.
What the hell happened to you?
I took care of your boyfriend.
My boyfriend?
The guy you've been screwing.
Killed him.
No, you didn't.
He's dead, Angie.
He's never gonna touch you ever.
I don't believe you.
Why not?
I've known you
since the third grade, James.
Even you couldn't do something
that terrible.
That's my Angie.
I brought you something.
This is what we're working for.
Bucket brigade.
Pretty clever.
You weren't too shabby yourself.
Why, thank you.
Dale.
Dale Barbara.
I'm guessing that's you.
Guilty.
Where'd you find them?
Uh, you know what,
they were actually
just right there,
where I left them, just hanging
over the mirror in you bathroom.
Huh. That's the first place
I checked.
I must have missed them.
How's he doing?
It's lucky Linda got to him
when she did.
Took in a lot of smoke,
but I think
he's gonna pull through.
Mind if I have a
moment with him?
What the hell you thinking?
You told me
to clean up our mess.
You call this cleaning it up?
How is he?
Well, there's someone up there
watching over him.
Thank you for saving me.
You're welcome,
but what in the world
were you doing in there?
I was, uh...
...getting a suit
for Duke's funeral.
I switched on a light,
and then I can't really remember
the rest.
Must have been a gas leak.
The dome's right there
in Duke's backyard.
Probably, uh, severed a line.
Well, we're just all glad
you're okay, Reverend.
Bless you, child.
Linda,
thank you for saving
the reverend.
I'm just...
I'm just doing my job.
Thank you, everyone,
for a job well done.
Well, we couldn't have done
it without you, Big Jim.
Ah...
I appreciate that,
but, uh, this isn't about me.
It's about all of us.
We stood together,
shoulder to shoulder,
like a town should
in times like these.
Now, this is not gonna be
the last crisis
that Chester's Mill faces,
but we'll get
through the next one
with the same courage
and solidarity
that we showed today.
Thank you all.
Like hell we will.
Go ahead,
pat yourselves on the backs
all you want,
but we're toast.
Great, you can put out a fire.
So what?
That thing...
that thing is trapping smoke,
and there's no way out.
Hey, come on, man.
Take it easy, Paul.
Back up.
Hey.
Don't you tell me
to take it easy.
You know, you're just like him.
You know, like, you're
lying to these people,
and you're promising that
everything is gonna be okay,
and it's not gonna be okay!
This thing
is never gonna go away,
and we're all gonna die!
Paul, don't!
Oh, no, no, Freddy!
Freddy?
Freddy, stay with me.
Freddy!
Breathe, stay with me, come on.
Stay with me, Freddy.
Freddy, Freddy.
Freddy!
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net